Guide to the Horace Walpole Collection
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Horace Walpole's Correspondence, 1725-1797; Series I; 12
  - Mann, Sir Horatio, 1st Baronet *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Mar 29 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 385-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Apr 26 (Box 22, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 390-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 May 3 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 392-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 May 17 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 405-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 May 31 (Box 22, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 410-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Jun 14 (Box 22, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 414-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Jul 12 (Box 22, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 421-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Jul 15 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 425-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Aug 9 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 429-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Sep 13 (Box 22, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 433-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Oct 20 (Box 22, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 440-42.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Nov 1 (Box 22, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 445-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Nov 16 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 453-55.
      With enclosure: Copy of a letter to Mr. Wood.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Nov 22 (Box 22, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 455-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Dec 6 (Box 22, Folder 58)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 461-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1760 Dec 13 (Box 22, Folder 59)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 463-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Jan 10 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 468-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Feb 7 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 474-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Feb 17 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 477-81.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Feb 28 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 481-83.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Mar 21 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 492.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Mar 28 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 492-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Apr 25 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 499-501.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 May 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 501-3.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 May 16 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 507-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Jun 6 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 510-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Aug 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 519-22.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Aug 15 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 522-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Sep 12 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 532-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Oct 17 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 542-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Oct 31 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 543-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Nov 21 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 550-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1761 Dec 12 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 555-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Jan 9 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 21, p. 563-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Feb 6 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 4-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Feb 27 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 10-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Mar 13 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 13-15.
      With enclosure: Billet to Palombo from Giovanni Lami.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Mar 27 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 18-20.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Apr 10 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 21-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Apr 17 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 27-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Apr 24 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 29-30.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 May 15 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 33-36.
      With enclosure: List of books requested of Horace Walpole by Horace Mann.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Jun 12 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 39-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Jun 26 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 43-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Jul 31 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 50-52.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Aug 7 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 61-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Aug 14 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 67-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Sep 4 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 74-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Oct 9 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 86-88.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Oct 23 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 88-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Nov 13 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 98-101.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Dec 4 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 105-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1762 Dec 25 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 111-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Jan 22 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 114-16.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Feb 26 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 117-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Mar 26 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 122-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Apr 9 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 124-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Apr 30 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 131-33.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 May 21 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 141-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 May 28 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 143-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Jun 11 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 149-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Jul 23 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 152-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Aug 20 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 156-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Sep 10 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 165-67.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Oct 1 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 169-72.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Oct 8 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 172-74.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Nov 12 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 178-81.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1763 Dec 15 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 192-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Jan 21 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 200-203.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Feb 18 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 203-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Apr 10 (Box 23, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 220-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Apr 17 (Box 23, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 223-25.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Apr 24 (Box 23, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 227-30.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 May 5 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 231-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 May 12 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 234-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 May 19 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 239-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Jul 7 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 244-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Aug 11 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 249-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Sep 22 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 254-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Nov 10 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 258-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1764 Nov 24 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 265-67.
      With enclosure: Copy of a note from Mr. Dagge to Horace Mann's brother, sent in 1759.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Jan 5 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 271-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Jan 19 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 278-80.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Feb 9 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 280-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Mar 23 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 285-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 May 4 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 290-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Jun 15 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 304-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Jul 27 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 312-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Aug 3 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 316-22.
      With enclosures: Copy of a letter from Horace Man to Lord Halifax, 2 Apr. 1765; Copy of a letter from Lord Halifax to Horace Mann, 25 Jun. 1765; Copy of a letter from Lord Sandwich to Horace Mann, 28 May 1765.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Aug 17 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 326-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Aug 23 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 328-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Aug 24 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 329-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Sep 7 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 333-36.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Sep 14 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 336-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Sep 20 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      With a pencil drawing of a Gothic arch.
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 338-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Oct 12 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 344-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Oct 18 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 349-52.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Oct 25 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 352-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Nov 1 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 354-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Nov 4 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 361-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Nov 14 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 366-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Nov 22 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 370-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Dec 14 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 373-75.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1765 Dec 20 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 375-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jan 3 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 377-80.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jan 10 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 383-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jan 17 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 386-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jan 24 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      With enclosure: Copy of a letter from Cardinal Torrigiani to Cardinal Stuart, 14 Jan. 1766.
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 387-91.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Feb 7 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 391-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Feb 15 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 397-98.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Feb 28 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 399-400.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Mar 7 (Box 24, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 405-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Mar 14 (Box 24, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 407-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Apr 5 (Box 24, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 411-12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 May 10 (Box 24, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 417-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 May 31 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 422-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jun 17 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 427-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jul 5 (Box 24, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 428-30.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Jul 19 (Box 24, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 437-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Aug 2 (Box 24, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 445-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Aug 23 (Box 24, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 447-49.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Sep 20 (Box 24, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 452-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Oct 14 (Box 24, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 456-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Oct 21 (Box 24, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 459-61.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Nov 18 (Box 24, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 466-68.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Nov 25 (Box 24, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 468-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1766 Dec 13 (Box 24, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 474-76.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Jan 10 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 476-78.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Jan 24 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 481-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Feb 14 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 485-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Mar 7 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 490-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Mar 21 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 499-501.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Mar 28 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 501-3.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Apr 18 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 510-12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 May 19 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 514-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 May 23 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 517-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Jun 6 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 525-27.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Jun 28 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 528-33.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Jul 11 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 535-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Aug 8 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 544-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Oct 9 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 555-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Oct 17 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 557-59.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Nov 21 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 562-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1767 Dec 27 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 573-75.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Jan 9 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 575-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Feb 9 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 580-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Feb 23 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 22, p. 582-84.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Mar 12 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 1-3.
      With enclosure: Copy of a letter from Stuart-Mackenzie to Horace Mann, 9 Feb. 1768.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Mar 15 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 4-5.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Apr 9 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 9-11.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Apr 23 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 14-16.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 May 7 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 17-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 May 17 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 22-25.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Jun 4 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 25-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Jul 2 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 34-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Jul 23 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 37-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Aug 20 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 45-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Aug 30 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 49-52.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Sep 6 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 52-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Sep 20 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 54-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Oct 18 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 59-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Oct 25 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 63-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Nov 14 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 67-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1768 Nov 28 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 71-72.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Jan 13 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 79-81.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Feb 24 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 88-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Mar 11 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 94-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Mar 25 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 102-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Apr 15 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 108-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Apr 29 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 110-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 May 23 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 117-20.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Jun 3 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 122-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Jun 27 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 129-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Jul 22 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 135-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Sep 1 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 139-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Nov 4 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 147-50.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Nov 28 (Box 25, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 153-55.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1769 Dec 18 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 159-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Jan 14 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 171-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Feb 2 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 184-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Feb 17 (Box 25, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 188-89.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Feb 20 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 190-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Mar 24 (Box 25, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 201-3.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Apr 14 (Box 25, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 203-5.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 May 12 (Box 25, Folder 58)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 213-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Jun 20 (Box 25, Folder 59)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 219-20.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Jul 14 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 221-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Aug 21 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 224-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Sep 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 232-33.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Sep 8 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 233-35.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Sep 22 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 237-39.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Oct 27 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 243-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1770 Nov 27 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 252-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Jan 14 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 260-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Feb 22 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 273-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Mar 15 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 277-79.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Apr 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 293-95.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Apr 13 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 295-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Apr 27 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 300-302.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 May 18 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 305-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 May 28 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 307-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Aug 24 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 317-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Sep 17 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 324-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Sep 24 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 326-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Oct 15 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 330-33.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Oct 18 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 333-35.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Oct 21 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 336-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Oct 29 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 341-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Nov 15 (Box 26, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 347-49.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Nov 29 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 351-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Dec 9 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 355-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1771 Dec 13 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 356-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Jan 25 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 369-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Feb 4 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 377-78.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Feb 15 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 383-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Mar 10 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 388-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Mar 28 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 392-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 May 9 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 404-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Jun 6 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 410-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Jun 13 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 413-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Jun 20 (Box 26, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 416-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Aug 11 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 426-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Aug 25 (Box 26, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 429-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Oct 17 (Box 26, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 437-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Nov 24 (Box 26, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 442-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1772 Dec 19 (Box 26, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 447-49.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Jan 30 (Box 26, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 456-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Feb 13 (Box 26, Folder 42)